İletişim Bilgileri

ozansahbenderoglu@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ozanşahbenderoğlu-983141aa (LinkedIn)

En Önemli Yetenekler

Object-Oriented Programming (OOP)

Unity

Game Development

Languages

İngilizce (Professional Working)
Türkçe (Native or Bilingual)

Honors-Awards

Atılım Üniversitesi İz Bırakan 50 Öğrenci

Honour Student

Ozan Şahbenderoğlu

Hepa Games şirketinde Co-Founder

Ankara, Ankara, Türkiye

Özet

I have Bachelor's degree in both Software Engineering and Computer Engineering. I have been playing video games since I was 5. Becoming a game developer was my dream when I was a kid. Now, I became one. I never thought of working in another industry. I started developing video games in 2012. I am experienced in Unity Engine and C#. Developed more than 20 games for Android, iOS and for VR.

Deneyim

Hepa Games Co-Founder Şubat 2021 - Present (1 yıl 10 ay) Ankara, Türkiye

MagicLab Game Technologies Game Developer Kasım 2019 - Şubat 2021 (1 yıl 4 ay)

ZİBUMİ Game Developer Ekim 2017 - Kasım 2019 (2 yıl 2 ay) Ankara, Turkey

Pixega Studio
Game Developer
Mart 2015 - Ekim 2017 (2 yıl 8 ay)
Galyum Blok - ODTU Teknokent

My main responsibility as a game developer is developing games for mobile platforms using Unity 5 game engine. To achive this, I have to mind performance issues of mobile devices and create solutions due to that issue. I use object oriented approaches during development. My other responsibility is coding game that can be understood by anyone that joins team at the middle of the project. I use C# as programming language and Visual Studio as

development environment. To sum up, I convert game ideas to working and beautiful games.

Simlab Eğitim ve Bilişim Teknolojileri Software Engineer Haziran 2014 - Şubat 2015 (9 ay)

Eğitim

Atılım Üniversitesi

Master of Science - MS, Software Engineering · (2017 - 2020)

Atılım Üniversitesi

Bachelor of Engineering (BEng), Computer Engineering · (2012 - 2015)

Atılım Üniversitesi

Bachelor of Engineering (BEng), Software Engineering · (2010 - 2014)